CLOSE

Privacy policy
==============

Your privacy is very important to us and we strive to make the collection, use and disclosure of your data as transparent as possible. We have drawn up this data protection declaration in accordance with the requirements of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection Act (DSG). Through this data protection information we inform you about the important aspects of data processing within the framework of our website.

This privacy policy tells you how we collect information about you when you use our products or services or otherwise contact i-Magazine AG (hereinafter referred to as "i-mag" - Yumpu.com). This privacy statement also describes how we use information about you based on your choices. You have the opportunity to object to certain uses of information about you. We also explain how you can access and update certain information. If you do not agree with this privacy statement, please do not access, use, or interact with our service.

1. Data protection
    ---------------
    
    1. How do we collect your data?
        1. Information you provide to us: We collect information about you when you enter it into our system or otherwise submit it directly to us. We collect personal information about you when you register for or subscribe to our service, interact with us in any other way, such as through social media, requesting information or assistance, providing feedback, posting comments on blogs or articles, posting on support forums, reading magazines, participating in surveys, or using a contact form. The collected data will be used within the scope of earmarking. If you send us personal information outside of this website, e.g. by e-mail, we cannot guarantee the secure transmission and protection of your data. We recommend that you never transmit confidential data unencrypted by e- mail. By registering, using and subscribing to our service, you consent to the collection of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may also obtain your information through our group or third parties with whom we do business.
        2. Some data (usage data) are automatically recorded. These data are predominantly not personal. Usage data is collected by recording how you interact with our products and services.
    2. Types of personal data
        
        | Category | Data |
        | --- | --- |
        | Name | First name\*, Last name\* |
        | Contact details | E-mail address\*, address\*, postal code\*, city\*, country\*, language, telephone number |
        | Invoicing | Company name, VAT number, e-mail address for invoice |
        | User identification | Username\*, password\*, User-ID\*, API Key\* |
        | Elektronische Identifikation | IP-Adresse\*, Account activity\*, Active sessions\* |
        | Personal details | Date of birth |
        | Internet | Website, blog, Facebook page |
        | Lokalisierungsdaten | Geographical location\* |
        | Data entered by the customer | This covers all other personal data that the customer can enter in the user-defined fields. |

        Required data to be able to use the service are marked with a "\*".
    3. Passing on data to third parties: We do not pass on your personal data to other third parties unless you have consented to this data transfer or we are entitled or obliged to do so by law and/or official or court orders. In some cases, we use external service providers to process your data on our behalf. These were carefully selected by us and commissioned in writing. They are bound by our instructions and are regularly monitored by us. Your data will only be passed on within the scope of order data processing. In the case of non-payment or a default in payment, we will be forced to initiate debt collection by a third party.
    4. Where do we process the information we collect? When we use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we usually transfer it to our servers located in Ireland (EU). We may also process your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA). If this occurs, we will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information and your rights. By transmitting your personal information, you consent to our storing, saving and processing your data outside the EEA.
    5. How can you access and update your personal information? You have the right to access the information we hold about you. You have the right to review and update your personal information. If you have reasons to believe that the personal information we maintain about you is not accurate, please log into your account and review your information. You can also use your right to data transfer in accordance with Article 20 GDPR to obtain your data in a common machine-readable format. If you would like a copy of the information stored about you, you can request and export this information in the section “Yumpu Information” of your account. Access to your personal data via our website with your password and access data is only possible for you. At your request, if required to provide our service if you need help using it, members of our team can also access it.
    6. Protection of your personal information: We will use our best endeavors to take reasonable precautions to ensure the security, confidentiality, integrity and availability and resilience of the information you provide. For this reason, we have implemented technical and organizational measures (TOM) to protect the personal information we collect about you. In addition, we follow security measures that require applicable data protection regulations. This includes storing, using and disclosing any information you have provided to us in a secure manner. We take measures to protect your information from unauthorized access.
    7. TLS-Encryption with https: We use https to transmit data in an eavesdropping save way over the internet. By using TLS (Transport Layer Security), an encryption protocol for secure data transmission on the internet, we can ensure the protection of confidential data. You can recognize the use of this data transmission security by the small lock symbol at the top left of the browser and the use of the “https” schema as part of our internet address (URL).
    8. We send two types of newsletters:
        1. The first category includes ideas and tips for your magazines (information, tips and hints), status information for magazine transmission (direct link and embed code for each uploaded magazine) and product information (new features and updates received by email). You have the possibility to manage these notifications in your account. Additionally, there is an “unsubscribe” button in every newsletter.
        2. The category of transaction e-mails includes important information (billing information and information about the payment method selected) that you need to use our paid packages. These e- mails cannot be deactivated.
        3. In the future, we reserve the right to also send newsletters to site visitors via in-app messages.
    9. Use of cookies
        1. i-mag uses cookies – small files with configuration information. They help to determine user- specific settings and to implement special user functions. The functions of the website can also be used without cookies, but some user-defined properties and settings are then not available. You can find more information about cookies in our cookie policy ([https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy)).
2. Log-files
    ---------
    
    Yumpu automatically collects and stores information in so-called server log files, which your browser automatically transmits. We keep these for up to one month and then delete them. These are:
    
    * Browser type and browser version
    * Used operating system
    * Referrer URL
    * Hostname of the accessing computer
    * Time of the server request
    * IP address
    
    This data will not be merged with other data sources. Processing is carried out in accordance with Article 5 Paragraph 1 letter f GDPR on the basis of our legitimate interest in improving the stability and functionality of our website. The data will not be passed on or used in any other way. However, we reserve the right to subsequently check the server log files if there are concrete indications of illegal use.
    
    1. Geolocalization  
        In order to provide you with special services (e.g. automatic pre-selection of your country-specific VAT), this website uses a geolocalization software developed by MaxMind, Inc. (14 Spring Street, 3rd Floor, Waltham, MA 02451, USA). This software analyzes IP addresses to determine your approximate location. Geolocalization is carried out exclusively on the basis of anonymous IP addresses. An exact location determination of the website visitor is hereby excluded. Please also note MaxMind’s privacy policy, which you can access here: [https://www.maxmind.com/en/privacy\_policy](https://www.maxmind.com/en/privacy_policy)
    2. Links  
        Our offer contains links to other websites. As a provider we are responsible for our own content according to the general laws. We do not assume any responsibility for third-party content that is made available for use, recognizably via links, and do not adopt its content as our own. We have no influence on whether the operators of other websites comply with data protection regulations.
3. Website analytics
    -----------------
    
    1. Google Analytics
        1. This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, Ca 94043, USA). The use shall be made on the basis of Article 6 paragraph 1 sentence 1 letter f. GDPR. Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website, such as browser type / version, operating system used, referrer URL (the previously visited page), host name of the accessing computer (IP address), time of the server request, is usually transferred to a Google server in the U.S. and stored there. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics is not combined with other data from Google. We have also added the code “anonymizeIP” to Google Analytics on this website. This guarantees the masking of your IP address so that all data is collected anonymously. Only in exceptional cases the full IP address is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there.
            1. We have enhanced the IP address masking ("anonymizeIP") feature on this website for both, our Google Analytics and Google Analytics integration, into your Yumpu Analytics account.
            2. IP address anonymization has been developed by Google to enable this website to comply with applicable data protection laws and the recommendations of local data protection authorities when they prohibit the storage of the full IP address. If you use Google Analyitcs for your magazines or your account, anonymous data will also be transmitted to you. IP anonymization or masking takes place as soon as the IP addresses arrive in the Google Analytics data collection network and before the data is stored or processed. More information on IP anonymization can be found at [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en) .  
                Google will use this information on our behalf to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide us with other services relating to website activity and internet usage. You can prevent the storage of cookies by making the appropriate setting in your browser. We would like to point out, that in this case you may not be able to use all the functions of this website to their full extent.  
                You can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including IP address) and from processing this data by Google. Download the following browser plug-in and install it ([http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)). As an alternative to the browser add-on, especially for browsers on mobile devices, you can prevent Google Analytics from capturing data (see 3.1.3).  
                Further information on data protection in connection with Google Analytics can be found in the Google Analytics help ([https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)).
        2. Google Analytics reports on demographic characteristics and interests: We’ve turned on advertising reporting in Google Analytics. The reports on demographic characteristics and interests include information on age, gender and interest. This enables us, to get a better picture of our users without assigning this data to individual persons. You can find out more about the advertising functions at [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3450482?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3450482?hl=en).  
            You can opt-out of using the activities and information in your Google Account by checking the box under Advertising preferences on [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)
        3. Google Analytics deactivation link: You can prevent Google from collecting further visits to this website. Attention: The deletion of cookies, the use of the incognito / private mode of your browser, or the use of another browser leads to data being collected again. [Disable Google Analytics](javascript:gaOptout()). Deactivate Google Analytics. An opt-out cookie is set to prevent your data from being collected in the future when you visit this website. The opt-out cookie is only valid in this browser and only for our website and is stored on your device. If you delete the cookies in this browser, you must set the opt-out cookie again (for more information, see: [https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/gajs/#disable](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/gajs/#disable)).
        4. We have entered into a direct customer contract with Google for the use of Google Analytics by accepting the “addendum to data processing” in Google Analytics. You can find out more about the Google Analytics data processing supplement here: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3379636?hl=en&utm\_id=ad](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3379636?hl=en&utm_id=ad)).
    2. Mouseflow  
        This website uses Mouseflow, a website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback, campaigns and similar features / functionality. Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, form fills (keystrokes) in non-excluded fields, pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type (first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language and similar meta data. Mouseflow does not collect any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser. If you´d like to opt-out, you can do so at [https://mouseflow.com/opt-out/](https://mouseflow.de/opt-out/)
    3. Visual Website Optimizer (VWO)  
        This website uses the analysis tool Visual Website Optimizer of the provider Wingify (Wingify, 14th Floor, KLJ tower North, Netaji Subhash Place, Pitam Pura, Delhi 110034, India) to learn more about user behavior on this site and to optimize the offer for users. Only pseudonymous data will be used or stored. If you do not want Visual Website Optimizer to store data about your use of our website, you can object to its use. By using the opt out link ([https://vwo.com/opt-out/](https://vwo.com/opt-out/)), a cookie is set for exclusion from the analysis tool. This opt-out statement applies until you delete the cookie. The cookie is set for our website under the domain mentioned, per browser and computer. If you use our website from several computers or with different browsers, we recommend, that you set the opt-out cookie for each computer and browser. You can object to the storage of your pseudonymous visitor data at any time for the future ([https://vwo.com/opt-out/](https://vwo.com/opt-out/)).
    4. Trustpilot  
        Your opinion is valuable to us. Your feedback plays a crucial role in our continuous improvement process. Customer reviews are particularly fruitful for us. For this reason, we offer you the opportunity to rate our service or our company via a rating service provided by Trustpilot at www.trustpilot.de. We use an interface to the independent rating portal Trustpilot, which is operated by Trustpilot A/S (Pilestraede 58, 5, 112 Copenhaben, Denmark). It is not possible for us to individually control or influence evaluation invitations. Only in this way a complete, independent and uninfluenceable customer evaluation for our company and our services can be guaranteed. The following data (surname, first name (if available), e-mail address, reference number and language (German or English) will be transmitted to Trustpilot for this purpose and will not be used by Trustpilot or disclosed to third parties. By clicking on the feedback smiley, you agree that we may share your information with Trustpilot. As a result, Trustpilot will send you an evaluation reminder if necessary. If you no longer wish to receive invitations from Trustpilot in the future, you can unsubscribe directly in the e-mail or revoke them by contacting the rating platform. Please note that this applies to all review invitations from all merchants using Trustpilot’s invitation service. If a rating is submitted by clicking on the link contained in the invitation e-mail, a user profile is automatically created at Trustpilot. This implies your acceptance of Trustpilot’s Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. These can be viewed on the Trustpilot website at [https://uk.legal.trustpilot.com/end-user-privacy-terms](https://uk.legal.trustpilot.com/end-user-privacy-terms) and [https://uk.legal.trustpilot.com/end-user-terms-and-conditions](https://uk.legal.trustpilot.com/end-user-terms-and-conditions) respectively. If you participate in this feedback system, your rating will be published on the [Trustpilot website](https://uk.trustpilot.com/review/). Further details can be found in Trustpilot’s privacy policy and terms and conditions. An evaluation of our company can also be carried out directly on the website de.trustpilot.com/review/. As a user / customer, you are free to give an evaluation. The creation of a user profile at Trustpilot is required for the submission of an assessment or the recording of customer feedback. In addition to an evaluation for the inviting company, evaluations for any company can also be entered on Trustpilot’s evaluation portal.
        1. We are using Turstpilot TrustBoxes to display customer reviews on yumpu.com. Trustpilot uses the so called "impression tracking" to check the number of times a TrustBox is loaded. Moreover, Trustpilot continuously tracks the speed performance of each TrustBox. Although IP addresses are being recorded, they are not stored. The IP addresses are transformed to geographic country data and are used for the sole purpose of creating a geographic performance analysis.
4. Google Fonts
    ------------
    
    1. We use Google Fonts from the company Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) on our website. Google Fonts is used without authentication and no cookies are sent to the Google Fonts API. If you have an account with Google, none of your Google Account information will be transmitted to Google while using Google Fonts. Google only records the use of CSS and the fonts used and stores this data securely. Among other things, Google Fonts improves the display of fonts, texts, characters and other elements. More on these and other questions can be found at [https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq](https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq). You can read which data is collected by Google and for what purpose this data is used at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).
5. Advertising
    -----------
    
    1. Google Tag Manager (GTM)  
        GTM is a solution that allows marketers to manage website tags through a single interface. The tool Tag Manager itself (which implements the tags) is a domain without cookies. The tool triggers other tags that may themselves collect data. Google Tag Manager does not access this data. If deactivation has been made at the domain or cookie level, it will persist for all tracking tags implemented with Google Tag Manager. The IP address provided by your browser as part of Google Tag Manager will not be merged with any other data held by Google. We have also set Google Tag Manager to transmit your data anonymously to Google for this website. This guarantees the masking of your IP address so that all data is collected anonymously. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there.
    2. Google AdSense (Google AdSense is not currently in use. We reserve the right to use Google AdSense in the future).
        1. _On this website we use Google AdSense, the advertising program of Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA). Data on the displayed advertising media and your IP address may be transmitted to servers in the USA and evaluated there. In AdSense, cookies are used to provide better advertising, the cookies do not contain personalized data. Google AdSense sends a cookie to the browser after each impression, click and other activity that leads to a call to the Google AdSense server. If the browser accepts the cookie, it is stored there. Third party AdSense providers may be able to place and read cookies in your browser or use web beacons to store information they receive from ad serving on the website. Web beacons are small graphics that enable log file recording and analysis that are used for statistical evaluations for online marketing._
        2. _How to disable cookies can be found in our cookie policy at [https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy). If you do not generally allow us to use cookies, i.e. deactivate them via browser settings, some functions and pages may not function as expected._
        3. _Disable Personalised Advertising  
            If you have a Google Account, you may disable personalized advertising on the site [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated). Even if you opt-out of personalizing ads, you may still see ads based on factors such as your approximate location delived from your IP address, browser type, and recently used search terms. You can read which data is collected by Google and for what purpose this data is used at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)_
    3. Use of Google DoubleClick for Publishers  
        This website uses the DoubleClick for Publishers ("DoubleClick"), a service of Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, Ca 94043, USA). DoubleClick is a platform for the placement, control and optimization of advertisements on websites. With the help of DoubleClick, we can reach website visitors who have previously been interested in certain content areas by analyzing the use of our website, as well on other pages of our website or on other websites within the Google display network (on Google itself, so-called “Google ads” or on other websites) and present advertisements based on their interests. For this, Google uses so-called DoubleClick-Cookies, which are stored on your computer. DoubleClick cookies do not contain or store any personal user data.
        1. How to disable cookies can be found in our cookie policy at [https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy). If you do not generally allow us to use cookies, i.e. deactivate them via browser settings, some functions and pages may not function as expected.
        2. You can deactivate interest-related ads from Google in your browser by clicking on the “deactivate” link in the “Deactivation settings” section of [http://www.google.de/settings/ads](http://www.google.de/settings/ads) or (if you use Google Chrome, Firefox or Internet Explorer) by deactivating the DoubleClick cookie for your browser by installing the extension offered on [http://www.google.de/settings/ads](http://www.google.de/settings/ads).
    4. Use of Google AdWords (Remarketing / Conversion Tracking)  
        Our website uses the Google AdWords service. Google AdWords is an online advertising program from Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain view, CA 94043, USA).
        1. We use the remarketing function within the Google AdWords service. With the remarketing function, we can present users our website on other websites within the Google display network (on Google itself, so-called Google ads or on other websites) ads, based on their interests. For this purpose, the interaction of the users on our website is analysed, e.g. which offers the user is interested in, in order to be able to display targeted advertising to the users on other pages, even after visiting our website. To do this, Google stores a number in the browsers of users who visit certain Google services or websites on the Google display network. The visits of these users are recorded via this number (cookie). This number serves to uniquely identify a web browser on a particular computer and so not to identify a person; personal data is not stored.
            1. How to disable cookies can be found in our cookie policy at [https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy). You can deactivate the use of cookies by Google by following link and downloading and installing the plug-in provided there: [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin). For more information about Google Remarketing and Google’s privacy policy, please visit: [http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). If you do not generally allow us to use cookies, i.e. deactivate them via browser settings, some functions and pages may not function as expected.
        2. We use conversion tracking when using the Google AdWords service. When you click on an ad placed by Google, a conversion tracking cookie is placed on your device. These cookies lose their validity after 30 days, contain no personal data and are therefore not used for personal identification. The information collected using the conversion cookie is used to generate conversion statistics for AdWords customers, who have opted for conversion tracking.
            1. How to disable cookies can be found in our cookie policy at [https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy). You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
            2. Disable Interest Based Advertising In addition, you may opt-out of interest-based ads on Google and interest-based Google ads on the web (within the Google display network) in your browser by selecting the Opt-out button at [http://www.google.de/settings/ads](http://www.google.de/settings/ads) or by opting out at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You can find further information on your settings in this regard and data protection at Google at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).
            3. If Personalised Advertising is deactivated on the Web, the following shall apply: Advertising is not personalized by Google. You continue to see advertising on the web. However, this is less relevant for you. You can’t hide ads anymore. The advertising you see may be based on the website you are visiting and your general location.
    5. We continue to use Google Analytics to evaluate data from double-click cookies and AdWords for statistical purposes. If you do not want this, you can deactivate it via the Ad Preferences Manager ([http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en)).
    6. AdvertServe  
        Our website uses the AdvertServe. Renegade Internet is the developer of AdvertServe (5 Mocasin Trail, New Castle, PA 16105, United States).
        1. AdvertServe is a cloud hosted ad server that provides publishers with a wide range of targeting and reporting capabilities across display, mobile and video platforms. An ad server is the ad technology that enables the management, serving, and tracking of an ad or internal promotion on one's digital properties. Ad servers decide, in real-time, the best ad to serve based on relevance, targeting, budgets, and revenue goals. Here you can find the AdvertServe Privacy Shield ([https://privacy.advertserve.com/](https://privacy.advertserve.com/)). This website provides users with information about the program along with an easy-to-understand privacy policy and option to contact AdvertServe with any questions. It also provides these users with a way to manage their privacy settings:
            
            * Opt-in or opt-out of data collection
            * View all of the data that has been collected about you
            * Change your dates
            * Download your data in a machine-readable format
            * Delete your data if you want to be forgotten

            AdvertServe has taken steps to protect personal data in the backend system, e.g. hashing or masking sensitive data fields in system logs. By keeping statistical data only in aggregated form, it protects the privacy of individuals, since aggregated statistical data cannot be traced back to a specific person. Information that is collected is the gender, age, income range and interests of the users.
        2. Data Collect
            1. Internet Protocol Address  
                AdvertServe uses IP geo-location technology to translate your IP address into an approximate geographic location that may include your continent, country, state/province, city, zip/postal code, designated marketing area, time zone, ISP and current weather data. This technology is anonymous and primarily based upon publicly available IP registration data.
            2. Mobile Advertising ID AdvertServe does not utilize mobile Advertising IDs (AAID/IDFA) at this time. Both Android and iOS provide options for limiting and opt-ing out of such tracking though ([https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en)). Android users can Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads and iOS users can enable Limit Ad Tracking if desired ([https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223)).
            3. Referrer URL  
                AdvertServe is able to determine which web site you are viewing by inspecting the HTTP referrer header sent by your browser so that just relevant advertisements is shown, that are based on its subject matter. The textual content of these web sites is indexed and perform keyword targeting to further improve the relevancy of advertisements is set. However, this is strictly NOT performed on pages which are dynamically generated (i.e. with a query string) or for any pages that exist behind a user-login form so that avoid extracting any information that may personally identify you.
            4. User-Agent  
                AdvertServe uses the information in the Accept-Language and User-Agent HTTP headers sent by your browser to identify your device type (i.e. Desktop, Tablet or Mobile) as well as your operating system, web browser and language preferences. This enables us to show you advertisements that are suitable for your device and written in your language.
        3. Deactivation  
            How to disable cookies can be found in our cookie policy at [https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy). You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
    7. Consent Management  
        We participate in IAB Europe's transparency and consent framework and comply with its specifications and guidelines. To this end, we use the Consent Management Platform (CMP) from Sourcepoint Technology Inc, 228 Park Ave S #87903, New York 10003-1502, United States, as a subcontractor. In accordance with the IAB Europe Transparency and Consent Framework, Sourcepoint is identified as IAB Europe ID #6. Sourcepoint's CMP allows you to grant us data protection compliant consent to process your data and to revoke such consent at any time. You may also object to the processing of data on the basis of our legitimate interest. Here you will find an overview of your setting options, the purposes and the third parties involved: [Privacy Manager](#) More information on data protection and the CMP is available on the Sourcepoint website: [https://www.sourcepoint.com/privacy-policy](https://www.sourcepoint.com/privacy-policy).
6. Social Media
    ------------
    
    1. Social Log-in  
        For the registration and for login to the Yumpu account, you also have the possibility to authenticate yourself with your existing profile on one of the following social networks: Facebook, X (Twitter), LinkedIn or Google - and finally register or log in.  
        For this purpose, you will find on the registration page or login page a corresponding button including symbols of the respective providers of the social networks supported by our website. Before a connection to the provider is established, you must expressly consent to the process described below and to the transfer of data: By clicking on the respective button, a new window (so-called app) is opened, where you have to log in with your login data for the social network.  
        After you have successfully logged in, the social network will tell you which data (name and e-mail address) will be transmitted to us for authentication as part of the registration or login process. If you have agreed to this data transfer, the fields required by us for registration will be filled with the transferred data. The data required by us for registration or login is your name and e-mail address. Your data will only be stored and used by us after you express consent to the use of the transmitted and required data.  
        In order to perform the authentication process for registration and login, your IP address will be transmitted to the respective social network provider. We have no influence on the purpose and extent of the data collection and on the further processing of the data by the respective provider of the social network. For further information, please read the privacy policy of the respective provider (Facebook see 6.2.3, X (Twitter) see 6.2.4 and LinkedIn see 6.2.5).
    2. Social Plug-ins  
        So-called social plug-ins from social networks are used on our website. Plug-ins for Facebook and Twitter are currently only offered in the Yumpu account for registered users. We reserve the right to offer social plug-ins at other locations in the future. The plug-ins are usually marked with a logo or the "Like-Button".  
        Share: We offer the possibility to share magazines on Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Pinterest or via e-mail or iFrame. This function is not implemented using plug-ins. For this reason, no cookies are set here on our website.
        1. Facebook Like-Button  
            By clicking on the like-button you leave this website and establish a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook servers.  
            Facebook receives the information that you have visited our site with your IP address. If you click the Facebook “Like-Button” while logged into your Facebook account, Facebook can assign the visit of our pages to your user account. Information about the data that Facebook Inc. subsequently collects can be found here: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)
        2. Facebook Pixels  
            We use Facebook pixels from Facebook on this website. The code implemented on this page can evaluate the behavior of visitors who have come to this website from a Facebook advertisement. This can be used to improve Facebook ads. This data is collected and stored by Facebook. The data collected cannot be viewed by us and can only be used within the framework of advertising placements. By using the Facebook pixel code, cookies are also set (see cookie policy at [https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie\_policy](https://www.yumpu.com/en/info/cookie_policy)).  
            By using the Facebook pixel, the visit to this website is communicated to Facebook so that visitors can see suitable ads on Facebook. If you have a Facebook account and are signed in, your visit to this website will be associated with your Facebook user account. You can find out how Facebook pixels are used for advertising campaigns at [https://www.facebook.com/business/learn/facebook-ads-pixel](https://www.facebook.com/business/learn/facebook-ads-pixel).  
            You can change your ad settings in Facebook at [https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry\_product=ad\_settings\_screen](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen) , you must be logged in to do this. At [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/de/praferenzmanagement/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/de/praferenzmanagement/) you have the opportunity to manage your preferences for usage-based online advertising.
        3. Facebook Privacy Notice  
            On this website we use functions of Facebook, a social media network of the company Facebook Ireland Ltd. (4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2 Ireland). Facebook.com is sponsored by Facebook Inc. (1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA). You can find out which functions (social plug-ins) Facebook provides at [https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/). By visiting our website, information may be transmitted to Facebook. If you have a Facebook account, Facebook can associate this information with your personal account. We would like to point out that as the provider of the pages, we do not have any knowledge of the content of the transmitted data or its use by Facebook. If you do not want this, please log out from your Facebook account. The Privacy policy about what information Facebook collects and how they use it can be found at [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).
        4. Twitter Privacy Notice  
            On this website we use functions of Twitter, a social network of Twitter International Company (One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2 D02 AX07, Ireland). This means that personal data can also be transmitted to Twitter. We do not monitor this data exchange and do not store anything about it. If you want to know more about the use of your data by Twitter, you can find all the information in the Twitter privacy Policy at [https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy). If you have an account on Twitter, you can change your privacy settings in your account settings at [https://twitter.com/settings/account](https://twitter.com/settings/account).
        5. LinkedIn Privacy Notice  
            We use features from LinkedIn, a social network owned by LinkedIn Corporation (1000 W Maude Ave, Sunnyvale, CA 94085, USA), on this website. As a result, personal data may also be transferred to LinkedIn. We do not monitor this data exchange and do not store any information about it. If you would like to learn more about how LinkedIn uses your data, you can find all the information in LinkedIn's Privacy Policy at [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy). If you have an account with LinkedIn, you can change your privacy settings in the account settings at [https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/](https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/).
7. Communication via Intercom
    --------------------------

    i-mag uses the communication tool Intercom of Intercom, Inc. (55 2nd St, 4th Fl., San Francisco, CA 94105, USA). It is a communication platform for direct interaction via chat or e-mail between website visitors and the Yumpu team. If you have any questions, we can use this communication facility to provide you with prompt assistance. If you have registered, certain personal data will be collected and passed on at regular intervals. Your details (browser type/version, operating system used, time of server entry, first name surname, telephone number, e-mail address, company name) are collected during registration on the portal and transmitted to Intercom securely via SSL encryption. i- mag also uses Intercom to analyse and evaluate the use of the website (e.g. usage data) in order to provide individual support for the use of the website and to optimize the website in terms of user friendliness. Intercom, Inc. is party to the EU-US Privacy Shield Agreement. This agreement aims to achieve a higher level of data protection for non-EU companies. More information about Intercom’s privacy policy can be found at the following link [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy). More information about Intercom’s use of cookies can be found at [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy). The general terms and conditions of Intercom (Terms of Service) can be found under the following link: [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms).
    1. Facebook Integration  
        We forward your private Facebook messages to our @yumpucom Facebook page to our Intercom inbox. By doing this, we keep all our customer / user communication in one place. The conversations in Intercom are therefore shared with Facebook. You will receive our reply directly in your Facebook message inbox. Here you can find the terms of use https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms of Facebook. [https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms](https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms) of Facebook.
    2. Twitter Integration  
        We forward your Twitter direct messages to our @yumpu\_com Twitter page to our Intercom inbox. So we keep all our customer / user communication in one place, the conversations in Intercom are therefore shared with Twitter. You will receive our reply directly in your Twitter message inbox. Here you can find the general terms and conditions [https://twitter.com/en/tos](https://twitter.com/en/tos) and the privacy policy of Twitter [https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).
8. Communication via Mailgun
    -------------------------
    
    We use Mailgun for sending transactional emails. Mailgun may process personal data such as your name, email address, and other information contained in the emails we send. This data is used to deliver emails, track deliverability, and ensure compliance with legal requirements. For more information on how Mailgun processes data, please refer to Mailgun’s Privacy Policy ([www.mailgun.com/privacy-policy](https://www.mailgun.com/privacy-policy))
    
9. Hotjar
    ------
    
    Our website uses Hotjar to analyze user behavior through heatmaps and user recordings. This data helps us improve the user experience. For more information on how Hotjar processes data, please refer to [Hotjar's privacy policy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy/).
    
10. Processing operations under shared responsibility; single point of contact.
    ---------------------------------------------------------------------------
    
    The processing operations for which we are jointly responsible with the other controllers include the following:
    
    * Collection of your data on the website using cookies and other technologies by us and our vendors
    * Transmission of your data (pseudonymous cookie ID, IP address) within an anonymous environment (so-called cookie matching process)
    * Auction of advertising space
    * Purchase of advertising space
    * Display of advertising on the website
    
    For more information on data processing under joint responsibility by other vendors, please refer to their privacy notices, which you can access from our “Privacy Manager”.
    
    In order to exercise your rights as a data subject, you can either contact us directly (our contact details can be found in the section "Contact") or contact the vendors mentioned in the "Privacy Manager".
    
    The Joint Controllers have also agreed that i-mag, as Publisher of the Website, will act as a single point of contact for the exercise of data subjects' rights against all Joint Controllers.
    
11. Your rights
    -----------
    
    In principle, you have the right to information, correction, deletion, being forgotten, restriction, data transferability, revocation and opposition. If you believe that the processing of your data violates the data protection law or your data protection claims have otherwise been violated in any way, you can complain to the supervisory authority. Of course, you also have the right to complain directly to a supervisory authority at your place of residence or at our company headquarters in Diepoldsau. However, we would ask you to contact us first. Misunderstandings or problems can certainly be solved most quickly in this way.
    
    1. Data Protection Officer  
        i-Magazine AG (Gewerbestrasse 3, 9444 Diepoldsau)  
        E-Mail: [privacy@yumpu.com](mailto:privacy@yumpu.com)  
        In the event of contradictions between the English and German versions of the Privacy Policy, only the German version shall be authoritative.

Last update: 2024-08-29.

products

Resources

Company

* Cookie settings

Cookie settings

Made with love in Switzerland

© 2024 Yumpu.com all rights reserved

Choose your language

×

Main languages

Further languages

×

Done

Performing this action will revert the following features to their default settings:

Revert Cancel

Hooray! Your file is uploaded and ready to be published.

Saved successfully!

Ooh no, something went wrong!
